[Music]
Hello Gas, welcome to our new blog and today we are
going to show you the cars
that we had repaired in the insurance, we are going to
show you what kind of
claims we got on it, whoever has
n't seen my previous blog, go and
see it first, I had told you how the accident
happened, what all, how all the things, we went to the showroom and got it
cleaned, so after that you will get to know about it, I
mean, in this video you will
see where we got the claim
in the insurance, I
mean, our car was damaged in four-five places,
so which all did they claim
for insurance, so brother, I will
tell you in this video, so you will have to watch this video also, only then
you will understand
how it will happen, so
Gas, let's go, let's leave our room,
ignore this, come on
[Music]
Car keys
Pandit ji is taking it
[Music]
We have parked our car down on the left in the parking lot, you
can see the gas, it looks
even better in the evening, this is at night
also, I will show you, if I come quickly these days,
now this  It's taking a lot of time,
this is also going down, one in front and where is the laptop
[Music]
If it is quick, then we will
go in it, keep
watching the blog, keep watching, how many thieves are there in the flood, what kind of games are there, we have to
chase here and there, for
1 hour and half an hour
only, I was on
our 16, it will take at
least 15 minutes
[Music] It must be a
dream of a poor man, I mean a man, like this video as much as you can,
subscribe
[Music]
towards the car
and the second
[Music] there was a
crack here, a
little bit, it didn't happen, if they were saying that a
complete new one would have to be put, otherwise they
fixed it
themselves, it has extras
and this door, all the things are small and I mean
people criticize Tata's service, but it is so
good that even small scratches were
visible here, like this here, like this,
they hit it in front of us, they were doing
everything right, so don't criticize Gas Kanta's
service, it's a good service
and good brother, the one from Aligarh,
I will tell you in the description  I will
provide you the link, yes brother had
assisted me, so you should go and meet him, he does
good work, I mean he will
listen to everything of yours, then sir, I mean do
n't complain like this, all the entire staff whoever is working
there, the scenery, everyone is helping, so there is a
small block here for the gas people, it was a
little different, so let's end it here
[Music]